siterubix.com 2014-02-09

# Our Policies - SiteRubix.com

### What is covered

This policy covers how SiteRubix.com treats personal information that SiteRubix.com collects and receives, including information related to your past use of SiteRubix.com products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that SiteRubix.com does not own or control, or to people that SiteRubix.com does not employ or manage.

### Information Collected

SiteRubix.com collects personal information when you register with SiteRubix.com, when you use SiteRubix.com products or services, when you visit SiteRubix.com pages or the pages of certain SiteRubix.com partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. SiteRubix.com may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register we ask for information such as your name and email address. Once you register with SiteRubix.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. SiteRubix.com collects information about your transactions with us.

SiteRubix.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, SiteRubix.com cookie information, and the page you request.

SiteRubix.com uses information for the following general purposes: to fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting.

### Information Sharing - We don't do it

SiteRubix.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission.

We transfer information about you if SiteRubix.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, SiteRubix.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Cookies

SiteRubix.com may set and access SiteRubix.com cookies on your computer.

* * *

### What can you do with your website?

Anything that is not harmful, illegal, or malicious!

Websites that are built on the SiteRubix.com domain are prohibited from doing anything illegal, delivering harmful or hurtful content, and cannot be used to perform any malicioius activity. Pornography or adult content is strictly prohibited and may be deleted anytime without notice.

We hold full control over disabling a website that violates any of the above, and have full descretion on any other issue that may be unforseen or covered directly within these terms of service.

Building beautiful websites that are legal, and that do not harm anyone or anything are absolutely allowed and encouraged!

### WealthyAffiliate.com

SiteRubix is part of the WealthyAffiliate.com Internet Entrepreneur community and requires a free Starter Account. All SiteRubix websites require the owner to have an account at Wealthy Affiliate and be in good standing. Any violations of the SiteRubix or WealthyAffiliate..com terms of service may result in the disabling of one's websites and removal of your account. Regardless of what "type" of account is held, we reserve the ability to act in good faith and protect our network from anything we deem that violates our terms of service.

There are absolutely no obligations to users of WealthyAffiliate.com or SiteRubix to continue with the service and an account may be closed by the user by discontinuing to use the service. 

### Hosting & Web Space

Hosting a website at SiteRubix.com is limited and at any time a website is not being actively used or updated we reserve the ability to remove that website from our servers to make room for other websites.
